coming into a great team, a great
organization with great players and
great people. Um, just coming in my my
veteran presence and uh coming in
competing.
>> What are some of those things that
you've learned that you maybe when
you're younger surprised you that you
can now relay to some younger players?
>> Yeah, just uh just stay committed to the
process. You know, I think is um
important. um the results I might not
show, you know, early on, but just
continue to work, continue to work hard,
and um just keep your mind, you know,
focused on on the details and um doing
the little things right.
>> Thank you.
>> Go ahead, Nikki.
>> Hey, Fan. Um what intrigued you about
Washington? Why did you want to sign
here?
>> Uh just a great organization. Um great
players, um a great organization, great
coaches. Um always been a um a standout
organization. And so it just draw me
close here and um I felt like it was the
right fit.
>> Do you know Bobby Ingram at all, the
receivers's coach, or have you had a
chance to meet him yet?
>> Yes, ma'am. Um I met him this morning.
So um it was a good meet and um he's a
great guy and I can't wait to play for
him.
>> Just you two on there so you can keep
going if you have anything.
>> Hey Van, I'm curious what what was it
like to have your wife go into labor
during the Super Bowl? Like what what do
you what do you remember from that?
Yeah, it was all a blur, you know. Um,
especially winning the Super Bowl and
having a son on the same day is uh one
of the best days of my life. Um, but it
was all a blur, man. Just winning and
rushing to the hospital to uh be there
for the birth of my son. It was an
experience, you know, I'll never forget.
And uh something that was very special
to me, man. So, um got the best of both
worlds in in one day.
>> When did when did like when did you find
out she was going into labor,
>> man? After the game. I didn't know until
at the game till um you know I found out
from um one of our PR people came and
just told me about it and I seen it and
um I just tried my quickest to get to
the hospital.
>> How many times have you been asked about
that since that video?
>> Uh a lot. A lot. But it's okay though. I
like reliving the moment so it's okay.
>> Cool. That's very cool.
Hey, as a receiver too, just on the
field, where, you know, can look at
stats, we can look at numbers, but where
do you feel maybe you're a different
receiver even in subtle ways?
>> Yeah, I just think I'm a reliable
target. I think um, you know, uh, first
I got to build, you know, earn the trust
of the coaches, earn the trust of uh,
Jaden and earn the trust of my teammates
before any of that can happen. But um,
you know what I'm saying? I just want to
come in and just use my expertise and my
strength and um you know, just been do
what I do since I've been in the league,
you know, and um but like I said, it's
stepping stones to that. You know, I'm
not going to get that all in one day. I
got to um just be where my feet are and
take it one day at a time. But, you
know, I think the ultimate thing is just
earning the trust of um people in this
building and knowing that um I can be
there.
>> Just your experience of of playing
I can't
>> you come into
a situation like this with David
coordinator.
>> Um I'm sorry, Miss Nikki. I couldn't I
couldn't hear. You kind of went in and
out a little bit.
>> Oh, sorry. Um you know, in multiple
systems, playing with multiple coaches,
how does it help you as you come into
this situation uh with first time
coordinator David Blau and everything?
>> Yeah. um you know, I'm I'm going to be
learning just like him. Um he's a first
time off offensive coordinator and this
is my first time, you know, with him on
the team. So, it's going to be learning
some learning for me, you know, too, as
well. But, um you know, I think it's
just um coming in, putting my head down,
and uh honing in on it and learning the
playbook. You know, I know he's going to
do a great job of installing it. I know
he's going to do a great job of
explaining it to us. So, just um just
keeping my ears open and um keeping my
eyes sharp and, you know, trying to uh
hone the playbook as fast as I can.
What is Washington getting a Piggle
Conquo?
>> Oh, they getting an explosive player. I
mean, I think you see the Yak and what
he can bring, you know, as a tight end.
Um, and also just a great person, too,
as well, you know. Um, you know, people
talk about the football player and
football aspect, but he's a great human
being, you know, an even better person.
So, um, excited to see him grow, excited
to see him, uh, come out and play and,
um, have more opportunities that he's
deserving of. and I know he's excited
for the opportunity and um you know he's
shown a lot of flashes how explosive he
can be as a player and as a pass
catcher. So um I'm excited to see him
this season.
>> Obviously there's an level of
athleticism that helps you be explosive,
but is there something else about him
that allow that makes him explosive?
>> Um I think it's just his mindset. I
think his mindset he's he's not going
down. I think uh once he gets the ball
in his hand, he's looking to score. Um
he's not going to let the first person
tackle him. He's going to make the first
person miss. you know, I think that's
his mindset and u he uses it on he uses
it on the field and you can tell, you
know, just how angry he runs and, you
know, how um he wants the ball in his
hand so he can make a difference.
>> I've kind of always wondered this about
receivers
when you you've played with multiple
quarterbacks at this point in your
career. Do you know pretty early on if
you're going to have a good connection
with that quarterback, if there's, you
know, your timing's pretty on point
together? Um or does it always sort of
take time for you guys to figure that
out?
>> Uh yeah, I think it takes some time, you
know. Um I think it's just, you know,
throwing a lot of throwing sessions, um
talking and um you know, just building
that rapport, you know. I think it's
just a lot of work that you have to do
with that individual and um you know,
that's what I'm here to do and you know,
trying to uh throw with JD and whenever
he's ready so we can kind of get that
chemistry down pack.
Cool. All right. Thanks, man.
>> Thank you. All right. You guys have a
great day.
toes. I